Guide to the New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Committee on Arbitration, 1820s-1973
  - Subseries V.2: Case Correspondence, 1914-1930
    Correspondence prior and subsequent to the resolution of an arbitration case was retained by the Committee on Arbitration and can be found in Subseries 2. These files consist of parties seeking information concerning their case, as well as advice on arbitration processes. Some disputes were resolved without the need for formal arbitration. Materials found in this subseries date largely between 1922 and 1927, and are arranged by case number in accordance with the filing system used during the tenure of Committee Chairman Charles Bernheimer.
    - Case1296 1922, (2 Folders) (Box 180, Folder 1-2)
    - Case 1297 1922 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Case 1298 1922 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Case 1299 1922 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Case 1300 1922 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Case 1301 1922 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Case 1302 1922-1924 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Case 1305 1922 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Case 1306 1922 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Case 1307 1922 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Case 1308 1922 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Case 1310 1922 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Case 1312 1922 (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Case 1313 1922 (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - Case 1317 1922 (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Case 1319 1922 (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - Case 1320 1922-1923 (Box 180, Folder 18)
    - Case 1323 1922 (Box 180, Folder 19)
    - Case 1327 1922 (Box 180, Folder 20)
    - Case 1328 1922-1927 (Box 180, Folder 21)
    - Case 1329 1922 (Box 180, Folder 22)
    - Case 1330 1922 (Box 180, Folder 23)
    - Case 1332 1922-1923 (Box 180, Folder 24)
    - Case 1334 1922 (Box 180, Folder 25)
    - Case 1335 1922 (Box 180, Folder 26)
    - Case 1336 1922 (Box 180, Folder 27)
    - Case 1337 1922 (Box 180, Folder 28)
    - Case 1338 1922 (Box 180, Folder 29)
    - Case 1339 1922 (Box 180, Folder 30)
    - Case 1341 1922-1923 (Box 180, Folder 31)
    - Case 1342 1922-1923 (Box 180, Folder 32)
    - Case 1345 1922-1923 (Box 180, Folder 33)
    - Case 1347 1922 (Box 180, Folder 34)
    - Case 1349 1922 (Box 180, Folder 35)
    - Case 1351 1922-1924 (Box 180, Folder 36)
    - Cases 1352 1362 1364 1930 (Box 180, Folder 37)
    - Case 1359 1922 (Box 180, Folder 38)
    - Case 1360 1922 (Box 180, Folder 39)
    - Case 1361 1922-1924 (Box 180, Folder 40)
    - Case 1363 1922 (Box 180, Folder 41)
    - Case 1364 1930 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Case 1365 1922 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Case 1366 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Case 1367 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Case 1368 1922 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Case 1369 1922 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Case 1370 1922 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Case 1371 1922-1924 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Case 1376 1922 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Case 1377 1922 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Case 1378 1922 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Case 1379 1922-1923 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Case 1380 1922 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Case 1382 1922 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Case 1384 1922 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Case 1386 1922-1923 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Case 1387 1922 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Case 1388 1922 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Case 1389 1922-1923 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Case 1391 1922-1923 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Case 1392 1922 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Case 1393 1922 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Case 1395 1922-1923 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Case 1396 1922-1923 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Case 1397 1922 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Case 1400 1922 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Case 1401 1922-1923 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Case 1402 1922 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Case 1403 1922 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Case 1404 1922-1923 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Case 1405 1922-1925 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Case 1406 1922 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Case 1407 1919-1924, (2 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 22-23)
    - Case 1409 undated (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Case 1411 1922 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Case 1412 1922 (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Case 1413 1922 (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Case 1414 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - Case 1416 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - Case 1419 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - Case 1420 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - Case 1424 1922 (Box 181, Folder 20)
    - Case 1425 1922-1927 (Box 181, Folder 21)
    - Case 1426 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 22)
    - Case 1428 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 23)
    - Case 1429 1923 (Box 181, Folder 24)
    - Case 1430 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 25)
    - Case 1436 1923 (Box 181, Folder 26)
    - Case 1437 1923 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Case 1438 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 27)
    - Case 1439 1923 (Box 181, Folder 28)
    - Case 1440 1923 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Case 1442 1922-1926 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Case 1443 1923-1924 (Box 181, Folder 29)
    - Case 1444 1923 (Box 181, Folder 30)
    - Case 1445 1923 (Box 181, Folder 31)
    - Case 1446 1923 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Case 1449 1923 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Case 1450 1923 (Box 181, Folder 32)
    - Case 1451 1923 (Box 181, Folder 33)
    - Case 1453 1923 (Box 181, Folder 34)
    - Case 1454 1923 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Case 1455 1923 (Box 181, Folder 35)
    - Case 1456 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 36)
    - Case 1457 1923 (Box 181, Folder 37)
    - Case 1458 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 38)
    - Case 1459 1923 (Box 181, Folder 39)
    - Case 1460 1923 (Box 181, Folder 40)
    - Case 1461 1923 (Box 181, Folder 41)
    - Case 1462 1923 (Box 181, Folder 42)
    - Case 1464 1923 (Box 181, Folder 43)
    - Case 1465 1922-1923 (Box 181, Folder 44)
    - Case 1466 1923 (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Case 1467 1923 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Case 1469 1923-1924 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Case 1470 1923-1924 (Box 181, Folder 45)
    - Case 1471 1923 (Box 181, Folder 46)
    - Case 1472 1923 (Box 181, Folder 47)
    - Case 1473 1923 (Box 181, Folder 48)
    - Case 1474 1923 (Box 181, Folder 49)
    - Case 1475 1923 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Case 1476 1923 (Box 181, Folder 50)
    - Case 1477 1923 (Box 181, Folder 51)
    - Case 1478 1923 (Box 181, Folder 52)
    - Case 1479 1923 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Case 1480 1923 (Box 181, Folder 53)
    - Case 1481 1923 (Box 181, Folder 54)
    - Case 1482 1923-1925 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Case 1483 1923 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Case 1484 1922-1923 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Case 1485 1923 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Case 1486 1923 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Case 1487 1923 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Case 1488 1923-1924 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Case 1489 1923-1925 (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Case 1490 1923 (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Case 1491 1923 (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Case 1493 1923 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Case 1494 1923 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Case 1495 1923 (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - Case 1496 1923 (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - Case 1498 1923 (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Case 1499 1923 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Case 1500 1923 (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Case 1501 1923 (Box 59, Folder 44)
    - Case 1502 1923 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - Case 1503 1923 (Box 59, Folder 45)
    - Case 1504 1923 (Box 59, Folder 46)
    - Case 1505 1923 (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - Case 1512 1923 (Box 59, Folder 47)
    - Case 1532 1923 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Case 1536 1929-1930 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Case 1537 1923 (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - Case 1538 1923 (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Case 1539 1923 (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - Case 1542 1923 (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - Case 1547 1923 (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - Case 1549 1923 (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - Case 1550 1922 (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - Case 1552 undated (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - Case 1556 1923 (Box 182, Folder 19)
    - Case 1557 1923 (Box 182, Folder 20)
    - Case 1558 1923 (Box 182, Folder 21)
    - Case 1560 1923 (Box 182, Folder 22)
    - Case 1561 1923 (Box 182, Folder 23)
    - Case 1563 1922-1923 (Box 182, Folder 24)
    - Case 1567 1923 (Box 182, Folder 25)
    - Case 1568 1923 (Box 182, Folder 26)
    - Case 1570 1923 (Box 182, Folder 27)
    - Case 1572 1923 (Box 182, Folder 28)
    - Case 1574 1923 (Box 182, Folder 29)
    - Case 1575 1923-1924 (Box 182, Folder 30)
    - Case 1576 1923 (Box 182, Folder 31)
    - Case 1579 1923-1924 (Box 182, Folder 32)
    - Case 1580 1923 (Box 182, Folder 33)
    - Case 1582 1922-1925 (Box 182, Folder 34)
    - Case 1584 1924 (Box 182, Folder 35)
    - Case 1585 1923 (Box 182, Folder 36)
    - Case 1586 1923-1924 (Box 182, Folder 37)
    - Case 1588 1923 (Box 182, Folder 38)
    - Case 1589 1923 (Box 182, Folder 39)
    - Case 1590 1923? (Box 182, Folder 40)
    - Case 1591 1923 (Box 182, Folder 41)
    - Case 1593 1923-1924 (Box 182, Folder 42)
    - Case 1594 1923 (Box 182, Folder 43)
    - Case 1595 1923-1924 (Box 182, Folder 44)
    - Case 1597 1923 (Box 182, Folder 45)
    - Case 1601 1923-1924 (Box 182, Folder 46)
    - Case 1607 1923 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Case 1611 1923-1924 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Case 1612 1923-1924 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Case 1615 1923-1924 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Case 1618 1923 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Case 1623 1924 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Case 1624 1924 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Case 1625 1924 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Case 1627 1924 (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Case 1629 1924 (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Case 1630 1923-1924 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Case 1631 1924 (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Case 1632 1924 (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Case 1633 1924-1925 (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Cases 1633 1334 1635 1924-1925 (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Case 1636 1924 (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - Case 1637 1924 (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - Case 1639 1924 (Box 183, Folder 18)
    - Case 1640 1924 (Box 183, Folder 19)
    - Case 1641 1924 (Box 183, Folder 20)
    - Case 1642 1924 (Box 183, Folder 21)
    - Case 1643 1924 (Box 183, Folder 22)
    - Case 1644 1924 (Box 183, Folder 23)
    - Case 1646 1924 (Box 183, Folder 24)
    - Case 1647 1924 (Box 183, Folder 25)
    - Case 1648 1924 (Box 183, Folder 26)
    - Case 1649 1924 (Box 183, Folder 27)
    - Case 1650 1924-1926 (Box 183, Folder 28)
    - Case 1651 1924 (Box 183, Folder 29)
    - Case 1652 1924 (Box 183, Folder 30)
    - Case 1653 1924 (Box 183, Folder 31)
    - Case 1654 1924 (Box 183, Folder 32)
    - Case 1655 1924 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Case 1657 1924 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Case 1658 1924 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Case 1659 1924 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Case 1660 1924 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Case 1661 1924 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Case 1662 1924 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Case 1664 1924 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Case 1665 1924 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Case 1669 1924 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Case 1670 1924 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Case 1675 1924 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Case 1678 1924 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Case 1679 1924 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Case 1680 1924 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Case 1682 1924 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Case 1683 1924 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Case 1684 1924 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Case 1685 1924 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Case 1687 1924 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Case 1688 1924 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Case 1689 1924 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Case 1690 1924 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Case 1691 1924 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Case 1692 1924 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Case 1694 1924 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Case 1696 1924 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Case 1698 1924 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Case 1699 1924 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Case 1701 1924 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Case 1703 1924 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Case 1704 1924-1925 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Case 1706 1924 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Case 1708 1924 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Case 1709 1924 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Case 1710 1925 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Case 1711 1924 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Case 1714 1924 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Case 1716 1924-1925 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Case 1717 1924 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Case 1718 1924 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Case 1719 1924 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Case 1721 1925 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Case 1723 1924 (Box 183, Folder 33)
    - Case 1724 1924 (Box 183, Folder 34)
    - Case 1725 1924 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Case 1729 1924 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Case 1731 1924 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Case 1732 1925 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Case 1733 1925 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Case 1734 1924 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Case 1735 1924 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Case 1736 1924 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Case 1738 1924 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Case 1739 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Case 1742 1924 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Case 1743 1924 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Case 1744 1924 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Case 1746 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Case 1747 1924 (Box 183, Folder 35)
    - Case 1748 1924 (Box 183, Folder 36)
    - Case 1752 1924-1925 (Box 183, Folder 37)
    - Case 1754 1924 (Box 183, Folder 38)
    - Case 1756 1924 (Box 183, Folder 39)
    - Case 1758 1924 (Box 183, Folder 40)
    - Case 1759 1924 (Box 183, Folder 41)
    - Case 1762 1925 (Box 183, Folder 42)
    - Case 1763 1924 (Box 183, Folder 43)
    - Case 1764 1924 (Box 183, Folder 44)
    - Case 1766 1924 (Box 183, Folder 45)
    - Case 1767 1924 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Case 1768 1924 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Case 1770 1924 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Case 1771 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Case 1772 1924 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Case 1773 1924 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Case 1775 1924 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Case 1779 1924 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Case 1781 1924 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Case 1782 1924 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Case 1784 1924 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Case 1788 1924 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Case 1789 1924 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Case 1792 1924 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Case 1793 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Case 1795 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Case 1797 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Case 1798 1924 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Case 1799 1924 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Case 1800 1924 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Case 1802 1924-1927 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Case 1803 1924 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Case 1805 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Case 1806 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Case 1807 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - Case 1810 1924 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Case 1811 1924-1925 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Case 1812 1925 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Case 1813 1925 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    - Case 1814 1925 (Box 50, Folder 43)
    - Case 1815 1925 (Box 50, Folder 44)
    - Case 1819 1925 (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - Case 1820 1925 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Case 1821 1925 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Case 1822 1925 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Case 1824 1925 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Case 1826 1926-1927 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Case 1828 1925 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Case 1829 1925 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Case 1830 1925 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Case 1831 1925 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Case 1832 1925 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Case 1833 1925 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Case 1835 1925 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Case 1836 1925 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Case 1839 1925 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Case 1840 1925 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Case 1841 1925 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Case 1842 1926 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Case 1843 1925 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Case 1845 1925 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Case 1846 1925 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Case 1849 1925 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Case 1856 1925 (Box 183, Folder 46)
    - Case 1858 1926 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Case 1860 1925 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Case 1861 1925 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Case 1862 1925 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Case 1863 1925 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Case 1866 1925 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Case 1867 1925 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Case 1868 1925 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Case 1870 1925 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Case 1871 1925 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Case 1872 1925 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Case 1874 1925 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Case 1875 1925 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Case 1876 1925 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Case 1877 1925 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Case 1878 1925 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Case 1880 1925 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Case 1882 1925-1926 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Case 1883 1925 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Case 1884 1925 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Case 1885 1925 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Case 1888 1925 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Case 1889 1925 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Case 1890 1925 (Box 183, Folder 47)
    - Case 1891 1925-1926 (Box 183, Folder 48)
    - Case 1892 1925 (Box 183, Folder 49)
    - Case 1894 1925 (Box 183, Folder 50)
    - Case 1895 1925 (Box 183, Folder 51)
    - Case 1896 1925 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Case 1897 1925 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Case 1898 1925 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Case 1899 1925 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Case 1902 1925 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Case 1903 1925 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Case 1904 1925 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Case 1905 1925 (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Case 1906 1925 (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Case 1908 1925-1926 (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Case 1910 1925 (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - Case 1911 1925 (Box 51, Folder 51)
    - Case 1912 1925 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Case 1913 1925 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Case 1915 1925 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Case 1916 1925 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Case 1917 1925 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Case 1918 1925 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Case 1919 1925 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Case 1920 1925 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Case 1921 1925 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Case 1922 1925 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Case 1923 1925 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Case 1926 1925 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Case 1927 1925 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Case 1928 1925 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Case 1929 1925 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Case 1930 1925 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Case 1931 1925 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Case 1932 1925 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Case 1933 1925 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Case 1936 1925 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Case 1937 1925 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Case 1940 1925 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Case 1941 1925 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Case 1942 1925 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Case 1943 1925 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Case 1944 1925 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Case 1958 1925 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Case 1961 1925 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Case 1962 1925 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Case 1963 1925 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Case 1965 1926 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Case 1966 1926 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Case 1967 1925 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Case 1968 1926 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Case 1969 1925 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Case 1970 1925 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Case 1972 1925 (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - Case 1973 1925 (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - Case 1974 1926 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Case 1975 1925 (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - Case 1976 1926 (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Case 1977 1926 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Case 1978 1925 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Case 1980 1925 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Case 1981 1925 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Case 1983 1926 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Case 1984 1925 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Case 1986 1926 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Case 1987 1926 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Case 1988 1925 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Case 1990 1925 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Case 1991 1925 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Case 1992 1925 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Case 1993 1925 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Case 1994 1925 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Case 1995 1926 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Case 1996 1925 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Case 1997 1925 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Case 1998 1926 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Case 1999 1926 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Case 2001 1925 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Case 2002 1926 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Case 2003 1925 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Case 2004 1926 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Case 2006 1925 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Case 2007 1926 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Case 2008 1926 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Case 2011 1926 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Case 2012 1926 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Case 2014 1925 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Case 2015 1926 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Case 2016 1925 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Case 2017 1925 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Case 2018 1926 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Case 2020 1926 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Case 2022 1926 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Case 2023 1926 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Case 2024 1926 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Case 2028 1926 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Case 2031 1926 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Case 2032 1926 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Case 2033 1925 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Case 2034 1926 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Case 2036 1926 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Case 2037 1925 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Case 2038 1926 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Case 2039 1926 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Case 2040 1926 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Case 2041 1926 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Case 2042 1926 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Case 2044 1926 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Case 2045 1926 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Case 2049 1926 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Case 2050 1926 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Case 2053 1926 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Case 2055 1926 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Case 2057 1926 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Case 2058 1926 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Case 2061 1926 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Case 2062 1926 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Case 2063 1926 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Case 2064 1926 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Case 2065 1926 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Case 2067 1926 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Case 2069 1926 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Case 2070 1926 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Case 2071 1926 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Case 2072 1926 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Case 2074 1926 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Case 2075 1926 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Case 2078 1926 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Case 2079 1926 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Case 2080 1926 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Case 2081 1926 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Case 2082 1926 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Case 2083 1926 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Case 2084 1926 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Case 2085 1926 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Case 2086 1926 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Case 2087 1926 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Case 2088 1926 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Case 2089 1926 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Case 2090 1926 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Case 2091 1926 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Case 2092 1926 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Case 2095 1926 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Case 2096 1926 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Case 2097 1926 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Case 2098 1926 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Case 2100 1926-1927, (2 Folders) (Box 54, Folder 41-42)
    - Case 2101 1926-1927 (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Case 2102 1926 (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - Case 2104 1926 (Box 54, Folder 45)
    - Case 2105 1927 (Box 54, Folder 46)
    - Case 2105 1927 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Case 2106 1926 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Case 2109 1926 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Case 2111 1926 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Case 2112 1926 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Case 2114 1926 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Case 2116 1926 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Case 2120 1926 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Case 2121 1926 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Case 2123 1926 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Case 2125 1926 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Case 2126 1926 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Case 2128 1926 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Case 2129 1926 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Case 2131 1927 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Case 2132 1926 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Case 2150 1926 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Case 2151 1926 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Case 2152 1926 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Case 2153 1926 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Case 2155 1926 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Case 2156 1926 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Case 2157 1926 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Case 2158 1926 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Case 2160 1926 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Case 2161 1926 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Case 2162 1926 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Case 2163 1926 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Case 2164 1926 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Case 2171 1926 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Case 2173 1927 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Case 2177 1926 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Case 2178 1926 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Case 2181 1926-1927 (Box 55, Folder 34)